# ADNAN MUHAMMED

### FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



+91 9072458959





www.linkedin.com/in/adnanmuhammed770

https://github.com/adnanmuhammed77

### PROFILE

A full stack developer specialized in functional components with a passion for developing innovative idea's that expedite the efficiency and effectiveness of organizational success. Well-versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly. Confident communicator, strategic thinker, and innovative creator to develop software that is customized to meet a company's organizational needs, highlight their core competencies, and further

### SKILLS

PYTHON DJANGO HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP MYSOL

LARAVEL C/C++ PANDAS MACHINE LEARNING **GITHUB** 

### EXPERIENCE

## PYTHON DEVELOPER (TRAINEE)

Inmakes infotech pvt ltd,kochi

JULY 2023 - OCT 2023

### · I have been training with diango frame work on python

- · Database administration and website design
- · Key responsibility:python,django,html,css,,flask,pandas

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Code CL pvt ltd .Kochi

JAN 2023 - JUNE 2023

· I have been worked as a frontend developer · Database administration and website design

· key responsibility:HTML,CSS,Javascripts

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER (INTERN)

Technovalley pvt ltd,Kochi

JULY 2022 -DEC 2022

· I pursued python full stack i developed multiple projects, including shopify website

· Database administration and website design

### EDUCATION

07/2019 - 04/2022 BCA - BACHELORS'S IN COMPUTER APPLICATION KERALA, INDIA

MAHATHA GANDHI UNIVERSITY MES college Nedumkandam

07/2017 - 03/2019 PLUS TWO - COMPUTER SCIENCE KERALA, INDIA

BOARD OF HEIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION MES heigher secondary school Vandanmedu

06/2016 - 03/2017 SSLC KERALA,INDIA

KERALA STATE BOARD

St.Sebastian's high school Nedumkandam

### **PROJECTS**

#### MOOSAPPILLIL CATERS& EVENTS

This mosappilli caters & events created based on python django framework. The is specially designed for booking the events and the list of services. Like every other e-commerce platform, allows customers of the website to view the list of the all menus and services.

MOOSAPPILLIL.COM

### OTHOR PROJECTS

HTTPS://MENSWARE.PYTHONANYWHERE.COM/SHOP/

HTTP://DAYTODAY.PYTHONANYWHERE.COM/

HTTP://TRAVELSOS.PYTHONANYWHERE.COM/

### PERSIONAL SKILLS

Team work
Front End Coding
Project Management Tools

Design Thinking
Problem-Solving
Punctuality

Good Communication
Back End Coding
Creative & Professional

### DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge.

### place: Ernakulam.kochi